Norbert Helmuth Mayer

Contact

helmuth.norbert@gmail.com

+45 22539447

Grøfthøjparken 33, 8260 Viby J, Aarhus

http://portfolio.mayerspace.com

https://github.com/NorbertMayer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/norbert-helmuth-mayer-88229a108/



Personal profile

A Multimedia Design and Communication graduate with passion and interest in modern web development. With 2 years of hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and web applications using modern technologies I am ready to enhance the working environment. I am very effective working in a team and working individually. My motivation comes from constantly wanting to improve myself as well as my work, to achieve a solid career.

Work experience

Intern: Front-end developer for Drupal 7 ecommerce website at Scandesign Media A/S, design and IT company

Period: 01 February 2017 – 30 April 2017

The internship was based mostly on understating the functionality of Drupal 7. The main tasks were to support the other senior developers by testing and fixing the responsiveness issues of the product. I worked on developing responsive layouts for web templates with Bootstrap and CSS.

Intern: Front-end developer for WordPress websites at CartGeneration, Marketing agency

Period: 01 June 2016 - 30 August 2016

Understanding the functionality of WordPress CMS and learning how to develop custom designed websites. Through the internship I had the opportunity to convert PSD mockups for custom WordPress websites. Used of custom post type, custom field type and third party integration.

Education

Erhvervsakademi Aarhus, Aarhus

January 2018 - present

Web Development, Top-up programme

Erhvervsakademiet Lillebælt, Odense

September 2015 – June 2017

Multimedia Design and Communication

West University Vasile Goldis, Baia Mare

October 2003 – June 2006

Bachelor degree in Psychology and Educational

Skills

Languages

Good knowledge: HTML5, CSS3, Sass

Familiar: JavaScript, TypeScript, C#

Frameworks

Good knowledge: MVC5, jQuery, Bootstrap,

Skelleton

Familiar: JavaScript, TypeScript, C#

CMS

Good knowledge: Umbraco, WordPress

Familiar: Drupal 8